{
    "priya_sharma23": {
        "password": "reallystrongpasswordpolicyforsure197898754231qwe21",
        "security_question": "pet",
        "security_answer": "test",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (X11; Linux x86_64; rv:130.0) Gecko/20100101 Firefox/130.0",
        "creation_date": "2024-10-02T18:10:10.589384",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "john_doe42": {
        "password": "Zx9#mK2$pL7@qR5&vB3*nH6!",
        "security_question": "city",
        "security_answer": "paris",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Windows NT 10.0; Win64; x64) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/91.0.4472.124 Safari/537.36",
        "creation_date": "2024-11-15T09:23:45.123456",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "emma_wilson87": {
        "password": "Uy6%tG9^fD2@wS8*kL4#bN1!",
        "security_question": "school",
        "security_answer": "harvard",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Macintosh; Intel Mac OS X 10_15_7) AppleWebKit/605.1.15 (KHTML, like Gecko) Version/14.0 Safari/605.1.15",
        "creation_date": "2024-12-03T14:56:32.987654",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "alex_johnson55": {
        "password": "Jm3$hF7#rT9!cX2@pW6&yN5*",
        "security_question": "car",
        "security_answer": "tesla",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (iPhone; CPU iPhone OS 14_4 like Mac OS X) AppleWebKit/605.1.15 (KHTML, like Gecko) Version/14.0.3 Mobile/15E148 Safari/604.1",
        "creation_date": "2025-01-20T11:11:11.111111",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "sarah_brown31": {
        "password": "Lq8%bK4#sG2@xZ6&mH9!vF3*",
        "security_question": "food",
        "security_answer": "sushi",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Linux; Android 10; SM-G975F) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/89.0.4389.105 Mobile Safari/537.36",
        "creation_date": "2025-02-14T22:22:22.222222",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "michael_taylor69": {
        "password": "Nh5#wR9$fT2!mB7@kL3&xP6*",
        "security_question": "movie",
        "security_answer": "inception",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Windows NT 10.0; Win64; x64; rv:86.0) Gecko/20100101 Firefox/86.0",
        "creation_date": "2025-03-30T03:33:33.333333",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "olivia_garcia12": {
        "password": "Ys7%pJ3#hG9!wF2@mN6&bK4*",
        "security_question": "book",
        "security_answer": "1984",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (iPad; CPU OS 14_4 like Mac OS X) AppleWebKit/605.1.15 (KHTML, like Gecko) CriOS/87.0.4280.77 Mobile/15E148 Safari/604.1",
        "creation_date": "2025-04-17T04:44:44.444444",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "david_martinez78": {
        "password": "Kw2$sH8#pL5!xN9@fR3&mT7*",
        "security_question": "sport",
        "security_answer": "soccer",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (X11; Ubuntu; Linux x86_64; rv:85.0) Gecko/20100101 Firefox/85.0",
        "creation_date": "2025-05-05T05:55:55.555555",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "sophia_lee25": {
        "password": "Bv9%nF4#tG7!qL2@xH6&wS3*",
        "security_question": "color",
        "security_answer": "purple",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Windows NT 10.0; Win64; x64) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/91.0.4472.124 Safari/537.36 Edg/91.0.864.59",
        "creation_date": "2025-06-26T06:06:06.666666",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "ethan_wilson93": {
        "password": "Rj6#mP9$fK2!wH7@xL4&nT5*",
        "security_question": "animal",
        "security_answer": "dolphin",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Macintosh; Intel Mac OS X 10_15_7) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/91.0.4472.114 Safari/537.36",
        "creation_date": "2025-07-07T07:07:07.777777",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "ava_thompson36": {
        "password": "Xm3%sG8#hL5!wN2@fT9&bK6*",
        "security_question": "singer",
        "security_answer": "beyonce",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (iPhone; CPU iPhone OS 14_6 like Mac OS X) AppleWebKit/605.1.15 (KHTML, like Gecko) Version/14.1.1 Mobile/15E148 Safari/604.1",
        "creation_date": "2025-08-18T08:08:08.888888",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "liam_anderson61": {
        "password": "Qp7#nH4$tR9!xF2@mL6&wK3*",
        "security_question": "country",
        "security_answer": "japan",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Linux; Android 11; Pixel 4) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/90.0.4430.210 Mobile Safari/537.36",
        "creation_date": "2025-09-09T09:09:09.999999",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "mia_rodriguez14": {
        "password": "Zs5%bG2#fN8!wT3@xH7&mK9*",
        "security_question": "subject",
        "security_answer": "physics",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Windows NT 10.0; Win64; x64; rv:89.0) Gecko/20100101 Firefox/89.0",
        "creation_date": "2025-10-10T10:10:10.101010",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "noah_clark47": {
        "password": "Jh9#pL3$sT6!xN4@fK8&wR2*",
        "security_question": "hobby",
        "security_answer": "photography",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (iPad; CPU OS 14_6 like Mac OS X) AppleWebKit/605.1.15 (KHTML, like Gecko) Version/14.1.1 Mobile/15E148 Safari/604.1",
        "creation_date": "2025-11-11T11:11:11.111111",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "isabella_wright80": {
        "password": "Vf2%nT7#hG4!wL9@xK6&mS3*",
        "security_question": "instrument",
        "security_answer": "piano",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (X11; Linux x86_64) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/91.0.4472.114 Safari/537.36",
        "creation_date": "2025-12-12T12:12:12.121212",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "james_lopez52": {
        "password": "Ck8#mR5$pN2!xH7@fT3&wL9*",
        "security_question": "season",
        "security_answer": "autumn",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Windows NT 10.0; Win64; x64) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/91.0.4472.124 Safari/537.36 OPR/77.0.4054.277",
        "creation_date": "2026-01-13T13:13:13.131313",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "charlotte_hill29": {
        "password": "Wd6%sK9#fH3!xN5@mT8&bL2*",
        "security_question": "drink",
        "security_answer": "lemonade",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Macintosh; Intel Mac OS X 10_15_7) AppleWebKit/605.1.15 (KHTML, like Gecko) Version/14.1.1 Safari/605.1.15",
        "creation_date": "2026-02-14T14:14:14.141414",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "benjamin_young63": {
        "password": "Lm4#pG7$tN9!xR2@fK6&wH3*",
        "security_question": "hero",
        "security_answer": "ironman",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (iPhone; CPU iPhone OS 14_6 like Mac OS X) AppleWebKit/605.1.15 (KHTML, like Gecko) CriOS/91.0.4472.80 Mobile/15E148 Safari/604.1",
        "creation_date": "2026-03-15T15:15:15.151515",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "amelia_scott18": {
        "password": "Hs8%nF2#bK5!xT9@mL3&wR7*",
        "security_question": "flower",
        "security_answer": "sunflower",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Linux; Android 11; SM-G998B) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/91.0.4472.120 Mobile Safari/537.36",
        "creation_date": "2026-04-16T16:16:16.161616",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "daniel_king71": {
        "password": "Yp3#sT8$fN6!xH2@mK9&wL4*",
        "security_question": "game",
        "security_answer": "chess",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Windows NT 10.0; Win64; x64; rv:89.0) Gecko/20100101 Firefox/89.0",
        "creation_date": "2026-05-17T17:17:17.171717",
        "blocked_by": []
    },
    "het": {
        "password": "het",
        "security_question": "school",
        "security_answer": "het",
        "user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (X11; Linux x86_64; rv:131.0) Gecko/20100101 Firefox/131.0",
        "creation_date": "2024-10-03T19:20:41.375303",
        "blocked_by": []
    }
}